Blueberry Cam

App icon
All lenses
Selfie lenses
Manual exposure
Manual focus
Add focus peaking
Focus loupe
Tap to focus
EV slider
AWB
Flash
Camera control
More histograms
grid
level/crosshair
Timer
Photographic styles
Macro
Portraits
Digital zoom
Lidar
Embed location
Save to folder
View outside frame
Console messages

Clean up UI:
Toolbar histogram + overlays z/p
Top bar readouts
Then file/MP/location/flash format
Camera view
Manual toggle, shutter, gallery
Double tap selfie switch
Double tap to set to auto
If custom value set then underlined/yellow background
Always show EV, if adjust SS or ISO then toggle manual exposure, disable EV and reset to 0
Histogram like halide, top right toolbar: icon->in toolbar->large overlay
Fix histogram data
Add capture control intent, and for lock screen/control centre/widget
Make custom sf symbol for control centre icon
Lock screen capture, when open real app adds photos taken to albums, and increase captureCount
Add settings
Default file format (share to locked view, need paid account)
Default histogram (picker) or none
Default should geotag location
Should show grid (add other grid options later)
Should should level/crosshair
Switching lens, resolution+file type changes (it is meant to be like this)

Future:
Localise for all iPhones iOS 26+
Improve memory/cpu usage, quicker camera switching
Move lens picker to bottom right
Click on any readout -> shows vertical slider right side screen like halide, slider shows the auto value constantly updating, manually changing it turns on manual mode, for ss/iso have left iso right ss?

Show proper selfie cameras
Tap to focus with focus EV
Front and rear photos simultaneously 
ProRaw

Swift 6

